<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Alchemy</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>

    <string-array name="categories_array">
        <item>All</item>
        <item>Animals</item>
        <item>Children</item>
        <item>Community</item>
        <item>Developing World</item>
        <item>Disability</item>
        <item>Elderly</item>
        <item>Environment</item>
        <item>Homelessness</item>
        <item>Illness</item>
        <item>Mental Health</item>
        <item>Religion</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="search_title">Search</string>
    <string name="about_title">About</string>

    <string name="confirm_yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="confirm_cancel">Cancel</string>

    <string name="server_url">"http://colmcoughlan.com/gci"</string>
    <string name="pref_previously_started">notFirstRun</string>
    <string name="sms_text">Alchemy needs SMS permissons to donate to charities. As you have denied it SMS permissions, Alchemy will now close - if you open it again you can change your mind.</string>
    <string name="welcome_text">Welcome to Alchemy, an app which will help you discover and donate to charities in Ireland. \n\n Tap a charity to see the donation options, and tap again to make a donation using your phone credit. You will get a message from the donation handling company confirming your donation was successful.</string>
    <string name="welcome_dismiss">Sounds good</string>

    <string name="about_summary">This is an app which collects charity donation phone numbers and presents them in a nice way to help you find causes you\'re interested in.\n
        The charity information is sourced from <a href="https://api.likecharity.com/charities/">https://api.likecharity.com/charities/</a> . All donations are processed by <a href="https://www.likecharity.com">LikeCharity</a>, who have no association whatsoever with this app.\n
        Currently this app is restricted to use in Ireland, but hopefully other APIs will be added soon.
    </string>

    <string name="disclaimer">Donations made through this app come out of your credit. Alchemy does not handle any of your money - it is sent straight to the listed donation number for the charity. Alchemy has no association with any of the charities, donation service providers or phone networks.
    </string>

    <string name="supported_countries_title">Country</string>

    <string-array name="supported_countries">
        <item>Ireland</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="supported_countries_values">
        <item>1</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
